Sister trip. Sister trip. And the little
brother and our other sister-in-law.
>> [music]
>> Hey guys.
Walking to our place, our room.
>> [music]
>> We're building M
on the way [music] to O.
>> [music]
>> I'm falling in
love with you, baby.
Everybody, let's all shout. Sister trip.
Sister trip. And the little brother
and our other sister-in-law.
We are just existing.
Existing. I miss you, Natalia, okay? I
miss [music] you so much.
Where are we? Where did you go? This is
exit, y'all. [music] Let's exit.
Oh, you know, I still can't stop
thinking about that
hash brown they made [music] for our
breakfast.
Do you want the house tour
or the
contour?
You want to stop me? First time
Coachella?
I think I
I don't know.
Just seven.
You have one onion.
What do you think so far?
The The onions are really good.
It's fresh. Yeah.
How do you like the burger?
Good morning, Coachella.
What is up? Today is day one. So, it's
Sabrina [music] or Sabchella.
And I'm just going to show you guys my
outfit. I forgot to show you guys how I
got ready, but anyways, [music] we're
out here and I'll show you guys what I'm
wearing right now.
Um where should I put you guys?
Happy Coachella day day one.
Okay, guys, [music] we're now here.
We're just taking pictures. Look at
them. They're taking pictures.
Um so, I'm wearing this dress because
this is my Sabchella outfit. It's very
like
pastel, very girly.
I'm going to go inside. So, yeah.
Period, guys. So, proud of you. And look
at my sister. She looks so [music] hot.
Okay, you're you're next.
Here. You're against the light.
Girl, work it. Hey.
Take my [music] crazy shorts.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god.
I love you, Coachella.
>> [cheering]
>> Let's keep this energy [music] up.
>> [singing]
>> You're really going to wear that?
Okay. Get off my back.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm seeing lion.
I like that one. Come on. We all kind of
grew up together, you know?
>> [music]
[music]
>> My sister and I are just exploring the
store and she told me [music]
that this
Can I see your guy? She has like a half
And I'm going to close [music] my eyes.
Put it on my head.
>> [music]
>> Deeply actually.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god, let me take a picture with
[music] this.
Oh, wait. My phone is dead.
>> Okay, whatever page I turn into is meant
for me.
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> Read the first line.
So, I changed my order. Well, I didn't
change it. I just added [music]
Madagascar vanilla to make it sweeter
because I like it when my matcha is
sweet. So,
>> [music]
>> let's try it.
I don't know. The guy just added it.
>> Favorite vanilla drink.
What is your favorite vanilla
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm so excited to
>> have arrived.
>> So, we're now here in
Blue Ribbon Sushi.
We ordered sushi. Where Where did you
get this at?
>> I always eat here when I'm in here.
>> It wasn't playing.
I thought [music] that was here.
Are you okay?
>> [music]
>> Are you okay?
>> I love [music] it. I'm obsessed.
And I really hope
I get to try
a really good bakery around the area
that sells like amazing donuts.
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> I want to try this.
It's different when it's on your skin.
Cookie.
>> [music]
>> This one
>> This one.
Oh.
It's not meant to be.
Not today.
Not today. But, good for you, Claudia.
Everything's like almost sold out.
Everything. I'll show you guys.
Everything
is like
almost sold out.
Everybody loves Rosebud.
Everybody.
Okay, so I just bought donuts [music]
from this place. I got chocolate and
strawberry.
It smells smells good.
>> [music]
>> Ooh.
Let's try them.
Ooh.
Cut up.
>> [music]
>> It's like
>> vanilla. Vanilla, though.
Chocolate donut.
The chocolate one.
>> [music]
>> I love that.
[music]
[laughter]
>> Okay, so I [music] got us pickles.
Literally it comes in different flavors.
Um [music] so let's try let's try honey
mustard.
>> [music]
>> Cheers.
>> Honey mustard.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like what I would taste in a
burger.
Put [music] this with burger and
sandwiches.
A perfect sandwich burger [music] and
Something.
Sweet meat.
Cheers.
Cinnamon, I don't
cinnamon
apple cinnamon
Something.
Sorry, Mom.
Classic meal.
More of [music] that, please.
So, this is our Uber going by. This is
our Uber. [laughter]
And this
I thought I was going to say Airbnb.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, and normal. I am.
>> So nice. Manifest. I will have a house
like this in LA.
I like a
Yes, you look baddie girl.
Hey.
>> [music]
>> Okay, we're just walking around the
street. My sisters are just taking
photos.
And my lips are still blue.
Dang, I'm cold. That's why. I was
supposed to go
up the apartment already, but
my sisters went down. They're like,
"After we're going to walk around. Do
you want to join us?" And I'm like, "Of
course, let's do it. You want to let's
hang out, but I wish you all got me a
jacket, cuz now I'm freezing.
I'm freezing.
Oh.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey guys, so I just got here at The
Broad Museum and I'm so excited because
it's literally next to that building.
Did you guys know that? It's called the
Walt Disney Concert Hall, designed by
Frank Gehry. I can't believe I'm here.
Um anyways,
uh first we're going to go to The Broad
Museum and then we're going to visit the
Walt Disney Concert Hall,
which is just over there. And yeah,
let's [music] have a good time.
Can't believe we're here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, so we're leaving this place.
I actually don't know what it's called.
I just thought I'm peeing.
And I was like
Ooh, I got a place where I can charge.
Also, I'm like cold. You guys can see it
from my lips. My lips are like blue.
Girl.
Why are my lips blue?
Cuz I'm cold. Oh, no, no, no.
Because I ate M&M's. The blue M&M's. So
cute.